[Music]
Hi, I'm Chad Hirsch. I lead AWS's global
market development for life insurance
and I also lead our generative AI use
case development for insurance more
broadly. And our team works with our
customers and our partners to ensure
that AWS's services and offerings are
meeting not only their technical needs
but their business needs as well.
We also have a wide array of solutions
in uh AI, ML, data uh and of course now
Generative AI and Agentic. And we also
build industry specific accelerators to
help our customers get more value faster
from their cloud and AI transformations.
The industry is one of the most ready
for what the new era of technology
around generative AI and Agentic is is
bringing in that it's one of the most
manually intensive old business
processdriven industries in the world.
And so the ability of generative AI and
of Agentic to take on some of those
manual processes and automate them or
augment the the people that that work on
those processes. I think it's going to
be a step change for the industry in
making it a more efficient more modern
industry.
We are substantial. We we have a good
footprint uh in Asia but our advantage
came from that differentiated thinking.
So the being customercentric being
customerled being that technology and
digital driven we all came with a
mission to um you know really changing
the way people feel about insurance. And
to me technology, digital and the whole
business plan around that has been
instrumental to to do the
differentiation.
After five years of working with FWD on
their as as one of their cloud
providers, we recently became their
preferred strategic cloud partner and we
are working on a 5-year uh agreement and
we are excited to help them with their
innovation and turning the cloud and AI
into a valuable asset for them to work
more efficiently and more closely with
their customers to provide better
service, better prices, better products,
etc.
[Music]